[dance music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[clink]
Omar.
Hey.
[both laugh]
[dance music]
[Yoli]
'Excuse me.'
Excuse...Hey.
Muvete, idiota!
Let me go!
[heel scrapes]
- What are you, blind?
-I'm sorry.
[cell phone buzzing]
[phone snaps shut]
[keys jangle]
[police radio chatter]
[siren blaring]
Ah. You look, uh,
marginally rested.
I was hoping I'd actually
get to REM. Sleep tonight.
There's another detective here.
Maybe you can go back to bed.
That's weird. Sac PD called
for help on this.
You two CBI?
Yeah, I'm Teresa Lisbon.
This is Patrick Jane.
Sergeant Henderson. Just holding
down the scene till you arrived.
I was in the neighborhood.
Two shots to the head.
No purse or ID on the victim.
The car's registered
to a Yolanda Herrera.
[Lisbon]
'Any witnesses?'
No, but these officers
responded to an anonymous tip
so somebody
had to see something.
It's from, uh, Luxure. It's
a, uh, club down the street.
She wouldn't be
the first club head
I've seen done
in by her dealer.
I applaud your certainty but I
don't think it's cut and dried.
She got the clothes right,
look at her hands. Short nails.
very sloppy paint job.
[Lisbon]
'Maybe she was in a rush.'
Doubtful. Free pass
to the champagne room
requires very careful
attention to detail.
You gotta be joking, huh?
I work these streets.
I know a club girl.
Apparently not, because you
missed a small bruise
on her left ankle. I'm guessing
she turned her ankle
trying to walk
in these shoes.
And her arms
are very well muscled.
Lisbon, correct me
if I'm wrong--
that appears to be
a sports bra she's wearing.
- I don't know. Probably.
- What are you getting at?
Well, your club girl here
was in a disguise--
A tomboy
trying to blend in.
The question is why?
And what was her game?
Is this really productive?
You knew her.
No, I didn't.
Your voice just pitched
a little higher like when
[Jane]
'you said you happened
to be around.'
Is he right?
Did you know the victim?
Of course not.
That's ridiculous.
Aha! I know who this woman--
this--this woman here--
okay. I'm here.
Hey, what the hell
is going on?
Yolanda Herrera
is an undercover cop.
That's exactly
what I was gonna say.
Yeah, big whoop for you,
smart ass.
No one can know that. It'll be
more dangerous for the next cop.
You're not known for
your management skills.
Work the case.
I'll help you where I can.
But Yoli's identity
must remain confidential.
And keep this circus act
under control, got it?
Got it. Yeah.
Wha--
Disappointing, Lisbon. I thought
you might push back a little.
Guy called me
a "circus act."
Hey. The man is grieving.
You push back.
- Okay, I will.
- Don't you dare.
- Okay. Said that I could.
- I take it back.
- Alright.
- Okay?
[inhales deeply]
I need a little rest.
[theme music]
[Officer]
'Yolanda Concepcion
was her real name'
but everyone
called her "Yoli."
She leaves behind a family--
Husband, two young children.
She's a valuable member
of my narcotics task force.
What was she doing
out here tonight?
She's supposed to be
getting friendly
with a dealer named Omar Vega.
He's a major player here
in South Sac.
We think his crew
is behind a
recent rise
in crime around here.
- You think Vega made her cover?
- Too early to tell.
But he's popped people for a lot
less than being undercover cops.
Okay. We'll start
at the club. Thanks.
Jane, meet me at Luxure.
[rock music]
What?
I can't hear you!
Still can't hear you!
Bye!
[rock music]
- Jane!
- Oh, hey, Lisbon!
Meet Vince Candide. He's our
host. He's a womanizing buffoon
but I think you'll be
amused by his presumption.
- What?
- Huh?
He..
This is...he..
Have you seen this woman?
What about Omar Vega?
Who?
[both]
Omar Vega!
Sorry. I gotta go run the place.
He can't hear!
Thanks, Vince!
If Vega's here,
he's over there.
[Jane]
'Thank you.'
Ah, that's more like it.
Pardon me,
have you seen Omar Vega?
You're never gonna
find him like that.
What do we got here?
[feedback whines]
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for your attention.
My colleague over there
in her not-here-to-party
clothes
is five-o.
Yeah, CBI.
She's looking for Omar Vega.
I have $500 in this pocket
for whoever can point him out.
That's 500 big ones
just to use your pointy finger.
And then we'll take it
from there.
Thank you. Party on.
Subtle.
But effective.
He's over by the bar.
[indistinct chattering]
You're someone nobody
wants to look at
so I'm guessing
you're Mr. Vega.
I like your swagger.
Well, thank you.
We're investigating
a murder.
No need.
I know what Yoli looks like.
I hear she got popped. Shame.
Was Yoli
at the club tonight?
You know the answer to that,
or you wouldn't be here.
- Did you talk to her?
- Yeah. Maybe.
- What did you talk about?
- Foolishness.
She's just another haina
from the neighborhood
trying to get my attention.
Hmm.
And did she
get your attention?
Did you take her outside?
No, ma'am, I did not.
I've been here all night.
Please, ask around.
No need.
He's telling the truth.
I've got nothing to hide.
Well, that's not
entirely true.
You're hiding
profound anger.
Is that right?
Mm. Mm-hmm.
The tension in your jawline
gives it away.
[Jane]
'What is it
that's bothering you?'
It's not a woman.
I don't think you care enough.
Not global warming.
What is it you covet most?
Money? No.
Respect.
This is a question
of respect.
Someone disrespected you,
didn't they?
How? What did they do
to you?
Keep guessing, pinstripes.
Pinstripes.Ma'am..
Are we done?
Yes, we're done, sir.
Whew.
Interesting.
Yeah.
I like the "pinstripes."
Vega took control of South Sac
in less than a year.
His competitors didn't agree
to work with him...
..they ended up like this.
Yeah, I see how
that could be persuasive.
No criminal record?
Vega's brutal and smart.
Always one step
ahead of us.
Ran his organization
like a terror cell.
Everyone knows what they
need to get the job done.
So his hands stay clean.
What was Yoli's assignment?
To find Vega's current base of
operation. It's always changing.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
- Where are we with suspects?
- None we can find.
I've a copy of the 9-1-1 call,
from a payphone
three blocks away
from the crime scene.
[woman on tape recorder
'9-1-1, what's your emergency?'
[Summer]
'Um, yeah, there's a dead chick'
on Kennon near 4th
in case you're interested.
Are there cameras
near that phone?
None.
Got a hit on the victims
missing credit cards.
Room charge, this
morning at a downtown hotel.
Take Rigsby. Yoli's cell phone
was missing, too, right?
Yeah, but the carrier hasn't
received a signal
since last night.
Whoever took the phone
powered it down
or pulled the battery.
Stay on it.
- You talked to the family yet?
- I'm headed there now.
What do they know
about Yoli's assignment?
Nothing. It's an ongoing
investigation, so they can't.
Understood.
[Lolo]
'I told her not to get involved
in this undercover crap.'
Desk jobs have benefits.
They pay good enough.
It was one of these
drug dealers, wasn't it?
I'm afraid I can't talk
about that now.
Still? Are you kidding me? What
does it matter now? My wife's--
[Jane]
'She's the greatest mother
in the world.'
Hello there.
Who is it? Hi.
Rafi?
[Elvia]
Rafi? Rafi?
Oh, there you are. I got him.
Sorry about that, Lalo.
This is Elvia, Yoli's cousin.
She moved in a couple months ago
to help with the kids.
He's a beautiful boy.
[Rafi babbling]
He doesn't know yet.
How do you tell a little kid
he won't see his mom again?
Did she talk to you
about her work?
No. But I barely knew what Yoli
was doing on a daily basis.
I'm sorry.
Why are we doing this?
To bring your wife's
murder to justice.
For you and your family.
Justice?
You think
my kids are gonna care
when some crack dealer
goes down for this?
They lost their mother.
I lost my wife.
For what?
War on drugs?
Give me a break.
[humming]
[pot bubbling]
Mm!
- 'That's a nice tune.'
- Oh! Ooh.
Didn't mean to startle you.
I'm sorry. What--what's cooking?
Spaghetti.
It's for the kids' lunch.
Ah.
You and Yoli must have
been very close
to help out
with the family like this.
Yeah. We were like sisters.
Really? I don't think so.
What?
The humming.
I hum. So what?
Well, humming--
it's like comfort food.
Takes us back to the breast.
And you are the mom
of the family now, aren't you?
Deep down,
you're glad she's dead.
What the hell
kind of cop are you?
Jane? What's going on?
I was about to ask Elvia what
she was doing
at Luxure last night.
The faded stamp on your wrist.
I have one just like it.
You followed Yoli
while she was working?
Elvia, what were you thinking?
I swear, if you did anything
to get her killed..
Why'd you follow her?
Uh, she has
a little thing for Lalo.
What--what are you
talking about?
I think she should explain.
Yoli didn't deserve you.
Look, I-I..
what I found in her jeans when
I was washing more than once.
Condoms. Yoli was on the pill.
I went to the club to see
who she was sleeping with.
- What did you see?
- Nothing.
I--she was in a rush
to get out of there
and texting somebody,
but I lost her.
We'll need you to come to the
office, make a full statement.
Might as well pack
your things before you go.
You're not coming back
in this house.
B-but...
I went there for you, Lalo!
Whoa.
Little more salt,
but that's pretty good.
Kids are gonna love that.
A charge was made, this morning
from a stolen credit card.
Let me guess--
husband on the prowl?
Killer on the run.
Oh.
[man #1]
'Uh, here we go.'
'One American breakfast,
three bloody marys'
delivered to room 618.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
[man #2]
Who's there?
Police. Open the door.
Just a minute!
[thud]
[beep]
Please don't shoot.
[groans]
I got it.
[Rigsby]
'Get up. Come on.'
can you pass me
a hand towel?
Step out of
the bathroom, please.
I swear to God, I've never seen
that woman before.
Oh, shush. Put that thing away.
What are you, a maniac?
You could hurt someone.
[Cho]
So, Summer, I need you to tell
me why you were making charges
on a murder victim's
credit card
hours after her death.
Cho...
that's Korean, right?
I also need you to explain
how you got that card.
Bad back, huh?
Yeah.
I can tell.
Is there anything I can do
to make it any better?
No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Look, I don't know anything
about any dead chick.
[click]
[woman on tape recorder]
'Yeah, there's a dead chick'
on Kennon near 4th in case you're interested.
[laughs]
Wow! You're way more slick
than the trolls that
usually bust my butt.
- Did you shoot the victim?
- No!
Did you see who did?
I heard shots. I ran to help.
She was already dead.
At least I called it in.
You ran to help?
Why wouldn't I?
Poor thing.
You took the victim's
credit cards.
This is about Omar Vega,
isn't it?
What do you know
about Vega?
Hmm.
I know that your dead girl
was hanging with him.
I also know that I've an 18-hour
window with a stolen card,
but you made it there
in record time.
You're after someone big.
Ahem.
Look, I know things.
Maybe we could make a deal.
- What do you got?
- What's your deal?
You give me something useful,
I'll drop the theft charge.
Pinkie swear?
Fine.
Vega just got his ass
handed to him.
The Perry Boys raided his
stash house a couple days ago.
- Cleaned out all his coke.
- How much?
Like ten keys, maybe more.
- The Perry Boys?
- Yeah. The Perry Boys.
Vega needs more product
and revenge fast,
or else his customers
are gonna be lost
and, uh,
he'll lose respect.
I bet you just doodle
in that thing, don't you?
[chuckles]
So. That's enough to
get me out of here, right?
I'll let you know.
So? Do you like her
for the murder?
[Lisbon]
'No, but I like her.'
What do you got?
Uh, text messages from
the victim's cell phone.
Yoli's cousin said she was
texting while leaving the club.
What was the last text she sent
before she was murdered?
Uh, "on my way.
Open the champagne.
Our favorite hotel?"
sounds personal.
Very personal.
Who's it to?
Uh, prepaid phone.
No record of the owner.
Her cousin might have been mad
about this affair business.
I think we should talk
to her boss again.
[intense music]
Excuse me. We're looking
for Sergeant Henderson's office.
- Towards the back on the left.
- Thanks.
That Yoli's desk there?
Yeah, that's where she sat.
Oh. Thank you.
[Patrick]
I'll catch up with you.
[Lisbon]
'Alright. Don't wander off.'
Wouldn't dream of it.
[intense music]
The text messages started
two weeks ago.
They paint a picture
of a pretty wild affair.
Did you know if Yoli
was romantically involved
with anyone on the job?
I can assure you,
Agent Lisbon
I keep a tight rein
over my undercover officers.
Then how do you explain those
texts? There's pages of them.
These aren't love tweets.
These are gang codes.
Yoli picked this up while
surveilling a gang
a couple months back.
Look--
See that? "champagne"
is cocaine,
uh, "on her way"
is someone's in trouble.
Who uses that code?
Nobody you ever heard of.
The Perry Boys.
A renegade stick-up outfit.
Two brothers and a cousin?
How do you know
about them?
I did some research when I found
out they hit Vega's stash house.
Vega was robbed?
Two days before Yoli's murder.
She didn't tell you about it?
I thought you kept
a tight rein on your people.
Look, nothing in
Yoli's surveillance reports
ever mention the Perrys.
Is it possible
she was working with them--
that's why she didn't
report the robbery?
She wouldn't compromise
her team that way.
Yoli wasn't dirty.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
I've one of my people
at her house now
looking for evidence
of an affair.
Van Pelt,
new marching orders--
Find out
if Yoli was on the take
or in contact with a gang
called the Perry Boys.
[clatter]
can I help you?
I'm sorry. I was trying
not to bother you.
But, uh, but since
you asked, yes.
Uh... who's that guy?
That's Trey.
Trey. Is--uh,
a fellow officer?
Yeah, we all came in
the same year.
So you and Yoli
must have been close?
That girl was my heart.
She was always there for me.
My partner seems
to believe that, um
that Yoli was
having an affair.
Nah. Yoli would never
cheat on Lalo.
Her family found condoms
in her pockets more than once.
We all carry 'em.
Never know when you've to
waterproof drug samples
when you're in the field.
Handy to know.
[indistinct chattering on TV]
Alright, mama.
Nap time is now.
Get in bed.
How much longer
is this gonna take?
I don't know.
Tell me what you're looking for.
Maybe I can speed this up.
My kids won't go to sleep
with you here.
I'm sorry, sir,
but I can't discuss the case.
Another Robocop.
Where do they find you people?
These are all family files.
Did Yoli keep
any private records?
Uh, a personal journal
or diary, maybe?
You can check her computer.
We already did, at work
and the laptop at home.
She didn't keep anything
important on those.
Too paranoid.
What computer did she use?
Right there.
Excuse me.
It's okay, Rafi.
The lady needs
to look at the computer.
She won't be here long.
[mouse clicking]
[instrumental music]
She'll be gone
in a few minutes.
[Lalo]
'It's okay.'
[instrumental music]
- 'Van Pelt.'
- Hey, boss.
Did you find anything?
[Grace]
'Yoli uploaded photos of a house
onto her kids' computer'
'the day before the crime.'
The photos link
to a foreclosure site
that show the house has been
vacant for six months.
The perfect place
for the Perrys to hide out.
We're gonna need
that address.
Daddy's home.
Hey! You must be Trey.
Hey. I must be.
Who am I waving at?
I'm one of the CBI people
investigating Yoli's murder.
Yeah? On our couch?
Well, you'd be surprised
what you can learn.
Really? Like what?
Well, this particular couch
it's very comfortable
on the first sit
but, uh, after time, gonna give
your back a lot of grief.
Hey, are you ready to go?
- Where we going?
- Tracking the Perry Boys.
- They may have killed Yoli.
- You want me to come?
- We got extra vests.
- Yeah, probably not my size.
- Why don't you wait here?
- That's great--I'll wait here.
Hold down the fort.
Good luck.
It's a whole new you.
Yeah. Be happy I wasn't
out there as a crackhead today.
Props include
urine-soaked pants.
[Jane]
'Charming.'
Uh, are those props, too?
Drugs? No.
These are the real deal.
I was out doing
hand-to-hands today.
You know, making buys
in different areas
see who
the current sellers are.
That's quite a haul.
Colorful.
What--what do you do
with the goods?
Everything goes
into the property room.
Investigation unit catches you
with as much as a crack pipe
in your car, they come down
pretty hard.
Mm.
Must be difficult
living two lives.
Well, you learn
to compartmentalize.
Mm. How was Yoli with that?
Yoli. God bless her.
She was one of the best,
actually. She had to be.
- You met her family, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she was putting that
husband of hers through school.
So Yoli was good,
but, uh, you're better?
So why is it that Yoli got
the, uh, Vega case and not you?
That's--
that's the big case, right?
Well, let's just say the short
dresses didn't hurt Yoli at all.
Tell you one thing, though,
I wouldn't have let Vega's men
do me like that.
You think Vega
had her killed?
[Terry]
'Aw, come on.
She's an undercover cop.'
This guy's
a notorious gangster.
How far have you really
gotta look?
'Sup, trey?
[Trey]
'You got it.'
- Oh.
- Oh, I am so sorry.
I'm sorry. Trey--
oh, that's embarrassing.
Mike, you got a towel,
a napkin or something? Come on.
That's terrible.
My bad.
Wipe that there. Uh, gonna need
another one of these, mike.
Okay, great. Thank you.
So clumsy.
I-I'm sorry.
[car doors close]
we're looking for Warren,
Dwayne, and Russell Perry.
Expect them to be armed.
They're erratic
and extremely dangerous.
- Van Pelt, you take the side.
- Yes, ma'am.
[intense music]
[gunfire]
[man groaning]
Police!
[man grunting]
[man #3]
We didn't come here
to work out. Don't move, kid.
[Lisbon]
Put your hands in the air!
[man grunting]
Uh! Aah!
[intense music]
[voice on TV]
'I did what I had to do'
Clear.
It's definitely
the Perrys.
[Voice on TV]
'I fought.'
[Grace]
'Hey, boss, I got one down
back here!'
[men grunting]
'nobody could help me.'
[door opens]
- Where'd all this come from?
- Mm.
Your friend Wayne
is so sweet.
Now there's a man
who knows how to smile.
Was he in a boy band?
You were right
about Vega.
So my information
was helpful?
No, but it was accurate.
You're free to go.
All charges are dropped.
Thank you, Agent Cho.
Kimball.
You're welcome.
You know..
...you should do something
about your back.
It's nothing.
You're very
invested in this
man-in-an-iron-face
routine, aren't you?
I bet I could make you
cry like a baby.
I'll bet.
There may be hope
for you yet.
[instrumental music]
Sac PD Narco unit just finished
searching the Perry's house.
They found baggies, scales,
drug residue, but no drugs.
Looks like Vega
stole his coke back.
The Perrys let the killer in
the house. Someone they trusted.
Otherwise, Dwayne would've
died with a gun in his hand
instead of
a video game controller.
Did ballistics come back?
Yeah, the .380 casings
found at the Perry house
match those from Yoli's crime
scene, all from the same gun.
ME puts the Perrys' time of
death the same night as Yoli's.
So whoever killed
the Perrys killed Yoli.
Great. We've got no suspects.
We're back to square one.
Well...
I wouldn't say
square one exactly.
No?
No.
[intense music]
Hey, Candide, we're ready.
[whirring]
[door clanks open]
That's quite an impressive
pile you have there.
What are you, uh, doing here?
I'm looking for you.
Well, you can't be
back here.
I can be wherever I wanna be.
Oh. Who says?
The law.
It knows no bounds.
What do you want?
I'm not sure yet.
Glad to see you're having
such a good week.
How much do you want?
Mm... 20.
- Grand?
- Percent.
That--that's insane.
Okay, then. Make it 25.
Get out.
I tell you what--
You tell Omar Vega
I got a deal to make
and we'll call it square.
I told you I don't know
any Vega.
No?
Then why are you
counting his money?
Vega uses this club
to launder his drug money.
It's his club,
that's obvious.
[Jane]
'Look at you.'
You're not a big time
club owner.
You tell Vega there's more
where that came from.
[phone beeps]
[intense music]
That pro seemed like
a piece of work, huh?
Who, Summer?
Oh, she's "Summer" now.
She is summer.
That's her name.
Just like she knows
your name's Wayne.
Look, it was just
some potato chips.
You emptied
the vending machine.
Yeah. She was hungry.
Copy that.
Hi. I was just leaving.
No. You're not.
No? I guess I'm not.
[hip-hopmusic]
we're up.
[music continues]
Whoa!
You mind turning
the bass down a little?
Makes me wanna
go to the bathroom!
You got a signal?
Yeah.
Just give 'em a lead
before you go.
[engine cranks]
[intense music
Straight.
Turn right here.
[music continues]
[Cho]
'I know this neighborhood.
It's derelict.'
It's a perfect place to set up
a drug operation.
[Rigsby]
'Okay, they stopped.
Slow down.'
They're just a few hundred
feet ahead. Let's park here.
How many months
has Sac PD's narco team
been looking for Vega's hideout?
We found it in one day.
[intense music]
I don't see the SUV.
They must have pulled into
one of these warehouses.
Yeah, but where?
Wait a second. Where'd you hide
Jane's tracking device?
His jacket lining.
[exhales]
Jane's jacket and shoes.
We're screwed.
We're fine.
Jane's screwed.
...So I was thinking
it's getting a little
crowded in here.
Walk away.
[Summer groans]
Right now.
If you wanted a date,
all you had to do was ask.
- Where can I find Omar Vega?
- Why?
He's got one of our people.
What makes you think
I know?
You're a hooker.
You had intel on Vega.
You must sleep with his men.
You don't mince
your words, do you?
- I don't have time for this.
- Neither do I.
I just spent an hour
talking to him.
You chased off big money.
Now I have to start
from the beginning.
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm arresting you
for solicitation.
Make sure
you make it tight.
I know how you love
to assert your authority.
What's the matter with you?
A life's at stake.
What is wrong with you?You
think you can come here
and take whatever you want from
me whenever you want it?
You're used
to getting paid. Fine.
How much do you want?
I don't want
your money, Cho.
I was just looking
for a little common courtesy.
Vega's held up at an abandoned
garage on Tenth Street.
Now, take these off of me
and leave me the hell alone.
[handcuffs clicking]
[instrumental music]
A little disappointed
about my shoes.
Is this how
you treat all your guests?
- What do you want to sell me?
- Drugs, of course.
You need a new supplier, or you
might end up shoeless yourself.
Este tontothinks
he's on one, yes?
So, um, this supply--
Where exactly
does it come from?
The narcotics task force
collects information
on every dealer in this city--
Where they operate,
where their stash houses are.
I give you that information
for a fee
and you can re-stock
your supply at will.
[laughs]
How is that amusing?
Oh, it's, um,
it's not funny "ha ha."
it's more funny crazy.
You see, I just got the exact
same offer yesterday.
Mm.
[laughing]
Interesting
negotiating tactic.
I'm gonna call your bluff.
Ah.
You think I'm lying?
There's only one rainmaker.
[sighs]
[clears throat]
Bring her in.
[Bianca]
'What are you doing here?'
Get your hands off me!
Yo! Where's Vega?
I demand to speak to him!
We're business partners!
What's he doing here?
Vega, what are you
doing to me?
I hate to break the news, this
woman's an undercover cop.
Yes, I know exactly what she is.
Actually, she's part of
the same narcotics task force
that you claim
to have access to.
Oh, you're good.
You're very good. She's good.
And you're being set up
for a one-way trip
to the gray bar hotel.
You patted her down
for a wire yet?
Vega, you can't be taking
this guy seriously.
No, to be honest, I don't know
what to make of you two.
I mean, it's not every week
that two dirty cops
show up on my doorstep,
both offering me the same deal.
I mean,
what are the odds, hmm?
Oh, the odds? The odds are
someone's lying. Shoot her now.
Then we'll talk
some business.
Like hell! He's not even a real
cop! This guy's a consultant!
No, you know, I think
that maybe my safest option
is to shoot you both!
Whoa! Wait a minute.
Just wait a minute.
Let's be cool here.
You can't shoot me.
I took out
the Perry Boys for you.
- Ah. Explain.
- They hit your stash house.
I knew where they were hiding
out, so I fixed it.
- As a gesture of goodwill.
- He is lying.
- You weren't there.
- Yes, I was. Ishot them.
That's impossible.
The gun that was used
to kill the Perry Boys
was the same gun
that was used
to shoot Yoli Concepcion.
I know you didn't kill her,
she was your best friend.
Yes, she was.
I loved Yoli. But she
was starting to suspect
that someone
in our unit was dirty.
It was just a matter of time
before she figured it was me.
Yoli was five-o?
Damn.
[Jane]
'That's a touching story.'
There's just
one problem with it.
I killed Yoli,
and I killed the Perry Boys.
I did 'em all.
Eenie meenie miney mo, hmm?
Catch a liar by the toe.
If they holler, let them go.
Eenie meenie miney...mo.
[Rigsby]
CBI! Drop the weapon now!
Everybody face down
on the ground now!
Don't even think about it.
[Rigsby]
'Yoli!'
'Don't move.'
Anyone happen
to see my shoes?
So, you're the one
who helped the Perrys
steal Vega's cocaine.
That's right.
When Yoli suspected
a dirty cop was behind it
why didn't she
come to me?
You're a bureaucrat.
Me and Yoli,
we came up together.
I was the one that sh--
I was the one she trusted most.
Look what it got her.
And you framed the Perry Boys
for Yoli's murder.
That's why you sent her the text
messages in code.
It was easy to get Yoli on that.
I told her if there was
a dirty cop on our team,
we should use code
so we didn't tip 'em off.
[Bianca]  The champagne text meant that I was in trouble.
Once I sent it, I had to wait for her to show up at her car.
[intense music]
You worked so hard to
frame them for Yoli's murder
and then you killed them
with the same gun?
Yeah, that part
wasn't planned.
I went to the Perry's
to split our take.
They wanted to revise
the deal.
Told me I had
to take a reduced cut.
Told me they'd drop dime on me
if I didn't give in.
I didn't give in.
I guess you showed them.
You don't get it.
Suits never do.
Try me.
I been in narcotics
my whole career.
Bustin' punks like the Perrys
that got more money in their
pockets than I make in a year.
It never ends.
So why try to beat 'em
when you can just join 'em?
Well, now you can
join 'em in prison.
Thank you.
hey.
What do you want?
Feeling bad now?
Roughed up
the down-on-her-luck call girl?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
I wanna use you.
Oh, be still
my beating heart.
Yes or no?
Okay.
Don't expect just because you're
a cop, you get a discount.
- Standard rates apply.
- Not for sex.
For information.
I can use a good
confidential informant.
Cash money, right?
Right.
You know, Cho,
I like you.
You got a mysterious,
feline vibe.
Is that a "yes"?
Kimball..
...for cash money,
I'd snitch on my mom.
What'd she do?
You got paper to sign, or what?
[instrumental music]
Oh, hey!
You don't look worse for wear
after your showdown with Vega.
Oh, I'm fine, apart
from a couple of holes
in my socks
from tap dancing.
You were right.
Your offer to Vega helped
flush out the real killer.
How'd you know it was Bianca?
Well, unlike her co-workers
Bianca never took off
her criminal disguise.
So it was a guess.
Ah, you make it
sound so artless.
- It's time.
- For what?
We need to talk
about Red John.
Oh. Grieving widower
at my 12:00.
Your 6:30.
- Agent Lisbon?
- Hi. Can I help you?
I'm looking for
the evidence room.
They're releasing
Yoli's things.
It's downstairs
two levels.
Sir?
Your wife's
undercover assignment
was to help take down
Omar Vega,
a drug dealer wanted
in connection
with multiple murders.
With what we learned
from Yoli
we found Vega's operation
last night
and we arrested him
with 20 pounds of cocaine.
I doubt he'll ever set foot
on the streets again.
Yoli saved
a lot of lives.
Thank you...
I guess.
[theme music]